andersenwindows.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy

**Last Revised on January 13, 2016**

**Andersen Corporation’s General Policy Regarding Privacy**

[Andersen Corporation](https://awwebcdnprdcd.azureedge.net/-/media/aw/files/thd/installation-andersen-materials---general-information-infolink.pdf?la=en&modified=20180507210554) and its subsidiaries and affiliates (hereinafter collectively “Andersen” or “we”) respects your expectation of privacy as you use its websites, blogs, social media sites, mobile apps, and online presence and for email sent and received from Andersen and its subsidiaries and affiliates.  This Privacy Policy applies to personal information and non-personal information we collect on AndersenWindows.com and any other official Andersen websites, including, without limitation, parts.andersenwindows.com, silverlinewindows.com, americancraftsmanwindows.com, andersenhomedepot.com, stormdoors.com, any Andersen mobile site, and any mobile applications, such as the Renewal by Andersen or Andersen Corporation applications available on your (or a third party’s device you may use) iPhone or Android operating-system-compatible mobile device that link to this Privacy Policy (the “Mobile Applications”), and any official Andersen sweepstakes entry forms on third-party sites and applications that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, all the foregoing are referred to as the “Site”).   

Andersen provides this Privacy Policy so you know about its online information practices and understand how Andersen treats the information it receives from and about you during your visit to the Site. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into Andersen’s Site Terms and Conditions of Use.  Renewal by Andersen LLC, a subsidiary of Andersen Corporation, has a separate Privacy Policy for information it collects on its sites and applications and such information collected by Renewal by Andersen LLC through its sites and applications will be governed by the Privacy Policy found on such Renewal by Andersen LLC sites and applications and not this Privacy Policy. 

**Personal and Non-Personal Information**

“Personal Information” means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to names, phone numbers, physical mailing addresses, email addresses, locations, credit information, credit card information, social security numbers, other contact information, or other information describing an individual. 

“Non-Personal Information” means information that does not specifically identify an individual or business, but includes information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your Internet service provider (ISP), operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address. Non-Personal Information is not typically used to personally identify you.

The Personal and Non-Personal Information that may be collected by Andersen is further described below.

**Information We Collect**

**Contact information**

We may collect the names and user names of our customers and other visitors.  Additionally, we may collect your purchase history, billing and shipping addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and other digital contact information. We may also collect information that you provide us about others. Andersen may collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you send an email or submit information via a form on the Site, Andersen may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, or any other information you provide.

**Communications with you/Promotions**

Andersen may also collect Personal Information if you communicate with Andersen via means other than the Site, including blogs, social media sites, or other online and offline communications. Andersen may collect any information you provide in any such communication.

Andersen values your opinions and comments, and we may conduct online surveys or polls. Participation in these surveys and polls is always optional. The information is aggregated and used to make improvements to the Site and to develop useful content, features and promotions for Site visitors. The identity of survey or poll participants is anonymous unless the survey or poll either specifically request Personal Information or otherwise states Personal Information is collected.

Andersen may occasionally request or require that you provide your email address or other identifying information to access portions of the Site or to provide you with communications. Further, Andersen may collect your email address or other contact information in an offline format (for example, your response to a mailer or filling out an attendance form at a trade show or for entry into a sweepstakes). By providing Andersen with your email address or any other contact information (such as your mailing address, name, phone number, etc.) you understand and agree that Andersen may from time to time use the contact information to send you information about products, services, our business, promotions, etc. Further, Andersen may pass along the information you provide to an Andersen dealer, distributor, or service provider who may contact you for various reasons, including but not limited to fulfilling orders or providing you information or assistance that you have requested.

The Site sometimes includes notices of promotions Andersen is conducting, and Andersen may permit you to enter electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion. Andersen may retain that information for communicating with you for future promotions or for any other purpose unless we receive communication from you in writing to cease sending you communications.

If you prefer not to receive this kind of information from Andersen, your request will be promptly honored. Please note, however, that any orders or requests for information made online, or other requests that necessitate a response, will receive confirmation emails related to the status of the orders or requests.

**Payment information**  
When you make a purchase we collect your payment information, including information from your credit or debit card, check, PayPal (or other payment service provider) account or gift card. 

Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention. Credit card information and other sensitive personal information required to process a credit decision is not used for any other purpose by Andersen or our financial services providers and will not be kept longer than necessary for providing the services, unless you ask us to retain your credit card information for future purchases.

**Returns information**

When you return a product or request a refund or exchange, we may collect information from you. In addition to any other uses noted in this Privacy Policy, we use the information we collect from you to help prevent fraud.  

**Demographic information**  
We may collect information about products or services you like. We might also collect information like your age or gender.

**Location information**

If you use our mobile websites or applications, we may collect location data obtained from your mobile device's GPS.  If you use our websites, we may collect location data obtained from your IP address. In addition to any other uses noted in this Privacy Policy, we may use this location data to find our nearest dealer location to you. 

**Other information**

If you use our websites, we may collect information about the browser you are using.  We might track the pages you visit, look at what website you came from, or what website you visit when you leave us.  

**Information Collected Automatically by Automated Means**

Andersen, like other website operators, uses analytic and reporting technologies to automatically record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, IP addresses, browser software, operating system types, clickstream patterns, the dates and times that the Site was accessed and other information provided through the software used to access the Site. Andersen may aggregate Non-Personal Information to measure how the Site is being used so we can improve its content.

From time to time Andersen uses “cookies” and other tracking technologies to, among other things, understand who is visiting the website. Andersen also uses the information for trends and statistics to improve the website and your experience at the Site. In addition, Andersen may track when a visitor opens our product catalog or other document in order to make it easier to move back and forth between the catalog or such other document and the rest of the site. Further, Andersen may contract with third parties who may provide content on the Site that collect cookies.

A “cookie” is a text file that may be used, for example, to collect information regarding a visitor’s website activities. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. With most browsers, you can refuse cookies by turning them off or requesting a warning prior to accepting the cookies. Depending on the content of the Site at the time, you may be required to enable your web browser to accept cookies to view or experience the full functionality of the Site.

Tracking technologies may record information, including but not limited to domain name and host names, IP addresses, browser software and operating system types, clicking patterns, and dates and times when the Site is visited.

We may use third-party Web analytics services on our Site. These service providers use the technology described in this section to help us analyze how users use the Site. The information collected by the technology (including your IP address) will be disclosed to these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Site. 

We may use the information collected through automated means to provide a better tailored shopping experience and for market research, data analytics and system administration purposes, such as to determine whether you've visited us before or are new to the Site, and for compliance with our legal obligations, policies and procedures. We also may use this information to target custom content and ads to you on this and other websites.

You may see certain ads on other websites because we participate in advertising networks administered by third parties. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of the technologies described in this section, and they use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests. The information they collect includes information about your visits to our Site, such as the pages you have viewed. This collection and ad targeting takes place both on our Site and on third-party websites that participate in the ad network, such as sites that feature advertisements delivered by the ad network. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.  Any uses described in this “Information Collected Automatically by Automated Means” section are not exclusive uses and there may be additional uses for such information elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collected Automatically by the Mobile Applications**

If you elect to install the Mobile Applications, the information we collect may include the following:

  * Your geographic location
  * Information about your use of the Mobile Applications
  * The type of device you use and its operating system
  * Identification details of your device (e.g., unique device identifier)
  * IP address
  * Your use of mobile coupons in a transaction

**Use and Disclosure of Personal and Non-Personal Information**

If you choose to provide Andersen with your Personal Information or Non-Personal Information by accessing the Site, Andersen may use that information in connection with its business, including, but not limited to, sharing that information with its subsidiaries and affiliates and also with third parties, such as, but not limited to, dealers, distributors, service providers, customers or potential customers, or Renewal by Andersen LLC’s non-corporate-owned affiliates. Andersen strives to comply with all applicable laws related to the protection of your Personal Information, privacy, and security.

Andersen may disclose your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information to any successor, assign, or business partner of Andersen. By accessing and continuing to use the Site, you understand that your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information may be disclosed to Andersen’s successors, assigns, business partners, dealers, distributors, or service providers.

Andersen may disclose your Personal Information to prevent an emergency, to prevent harm to others, to respond to legal requirements, to protect or enforce our rights and policies, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order).

Andersen contracts and uses third parties from time to time to provide, maintain, and improve the Site. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. We cannot guarantee that such third parties will not disclose your Personal Information.

Andersen may disclose Non-Personal Information to various third parties. You may not opt-out of the sharing of this information.

**Security**

Andersen follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to Andersen. Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Andersen or on its behalf, Andersen takes reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

Andersen may from time to time use third parties to provide content or deliver services, such as but not limited to e-commerce technology. Andersen follows generally accepted industry standards in selecting these third parties, but does not have ultimate control over the security measures used by those third parties.

Moreover, no method of transmission over the Internet or storage of information is guaranteed secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Access to and use of password protected and/or secure areas of the website is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized individuals attempting to access these areas of the Site may be subject to criminal prosecution or civil damages.

**Access and Updating Personal Information**

To the extent that you provide Andersen with Personal Information, you may request that Andersen update that information. For your protection, you may be required to provide proof of your identity to access or update your Personal Information. In order to access or update your Personal Information, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to webmaster@andersenwindows.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.

**Third Party Services**

Andersen may use third party services on the Site to provide you a better online experience or for other reasons. You may also be able to access third party websites, including dealer websites directly from the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites, including when you access third party websites or content from links on the Site. Andersen cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.

**Children's Privacy**

The Site is not structured nor intended for users under 18 years of age. Accordingly, Andersen will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children that Andersen knows to be under the age of 18.

**Applications for Employment**

Andersen may from time to time place job openings on the Site that allow you to provide Andersen with your Personal Information. We collect your information, including Personal Information and information related to your applicable experience through online forms or other means. We may also collect contact instructions through online forms or other means. 

**Changes**

Andersen may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. If Andersen decides to change its privacy policy, Andersen will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how Andersen uses it, and under what circumstances Andersen discloses it.  All changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective immediately upon posting to the Site.

**Your Consent**

By using the Site, you consent to the terms of the Andersen Privacy Policy and to Andersen’s processing and use of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for the purposes provided in the Privacy Policy. You further consent to reviewing the Privacy Policy from time to time to view any updates.

## Notice to California Customers

If you live in California and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a list of the personal information we have shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. We will also give you a list of the third parties that have received your information.  You can make a request one time each year.

To exercise your rights, you can email us or write to us at the address below. Mention in your letter or e-mail that you are making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. We will respond within 30 days.

Andersen Corporation

Attention: Legal Department

100 Fourth Avenue North

Bayport, MN 55003

legal-notices@andersencorp.com
